<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Gracia Yunruo Dong</title>
        <link>https://graciadong.github.io/month/</link>
        <description>Latest blog posts from Gracia Yunruo Dong</description>

        
        <language>en-us</language>
        

        

        

        

        

        
        <atom:link href="https://graciadong.github.io/month/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        

        
            
        <item>
          <title>Statement of Equity, Diversity and Inclusivity (EDI)</title>
          <link>https://graciadong.github.io/blog/2023/09/statement-of-equity-diversity-and-inclusivity-edi/</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>https://graciadong.github.io/blog/2023/09/statement-of-equity-diversity-and-inclusivity-edi/</guid>
          <description>This document outlines my experience, approach, and goals for fostering an inclusive teaching and learning environment.
As a racialized, disabled woman studying mathematics, my undergraduate and graduate experiences have greatly benefited from supportive professors and mentors. This was especially important during the final year of my PhD and during my current postdoc position while balancing my work with being a new mother. My mentors allowed me to work flexible hours and kept me updated with virtual networking opportunities and conferences, which contributed greatly to me succeeding in my roles.</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>Statement of Teaching Philosophy</title>
          <link>https://graciadong.github.io/blog/2023/09/statement-of-teaching-philosophy/</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>https://graciadong.github.io/blog/2023/09/statement-of-teaching-philosophy/</guid>
          <description>This document outlines my teaching philosophy and the standards that I hold myself to as an instructor.
In my teaching and mentoring roles, my goal is to inspire students to succeed in their future academic pursuits as well as their workplaces. To this end, I focus on the following key principles: motivation, alleviating performance anxiety, and fostering peer learning and help-seeking behaviours.
I motivate students in my classes by emphasizing real-world applications in my lessons.</description>
        </item>
            
        
    </channel>
</rss>
